The Rainbow Bubble Maker Jukebox 5000

Play button:
This plays the songs that have been selected in the queue. Play button also is a pause button. When you hit the play button, it 
starts the song. Hit the play button again and it pauses the song. Hit play again and the song picks up from where it was paused.

Stop button:
This stops the song from playing. When play button is clicked again, Song begins to play again from the beginning of the song.

Clear queue button:
As you glance at the top right corner, you will see the number of songs in the queue. This is the play list of songs you added by 
clicking "Add song" button. The clear queue button will delete all the songs in you playlist (queue). This includes the song that 
is currently playing. Also the clear queue button stops whatever effects that were animated during the song.

Add song button:
This is where you initally start the song's play. You click the "Add songs" button, then select the song you would like played. The 
"Add songs" button defaults to the music folder. If the song desired isn't in the music folder, you will have to navigate to it's 
folder & select it. Once selected the song it added to the queue and the number of songs in the queue is displayed in the top right 
corner.

More songs can be added to the queue by simply clicking "Add songs" again and repeating the previous instuctions. You can confirm 
that the song was added to the queue by again glancing to the top right corner. There you will see that the queue number has 
increased by 1.

Songs in the queue will only be played once.


OPTIONS MENU:

Beat sensitivity:
This option triggers the action of the effects. It governs the change of direction; the speed of the effect; and how often the 
effect is triggered.

Number of balls: 
This is where you decide the number of balls that will be drawn to the screen at one time.

Background:
The background can be selected by choosing the correct background listed:
a. none
	Background is all black. If effects are selected, they will be drawn over itself.

b. black
	The background is all black. All effects drawn will have a lighter color in order to see the effect in contrast with the 	
	dark background.

c. white
	The background is all white. All effects drawn will have a darker color in order to see the
	effect in contrast with the light background.

d. strobe
	This background starts in all black and switches to white and back. Giving the illusion of a strobe light effect.

e. disco
	This background starts with a disco print that moves from left to right, giving the effect of a disco hall.

Effects:
a. Bubbles
	This effect is circles in various diameters moving across the screen, then appear to bounce back into the opposite 		
	direction.

b. Explosions
	This effect has the bubbles but now have the illusion of breaking apart into smaller diameter circles

c. Waveform
	This effect is an abstract representation of the music signal in the illusion of a wave effect.

d. Infinite Mirror
	This effect is the mirror tunnel effect. It is one fully reflective mirror and one "one way" mirror, set up so that the 	
	one-way or partially reflective mirror reflects an image back onto the fully reflective mirror, in a recursive manner, 		
	creating a series of smaller and smaller reflections that recede into an infinite distance. 

e. Fill bubbles
	This effect is just as discribed. It fills the bubbles with their particular color.

Menu option instructions:
1) To set the beat sensitivity, type the desired number in the text field, hit the set button. Note: the smaller the number the     
  more actions will be performed.

2) To set the number of bubbles, type the desired number in the text field, then hit the set button. Note: smaller number of balls  
   are recommended for slower computers.

3) To set the background, just choose from choices. There can only be one background at a time.

4) To set the effects, just put a check in box of your choice. The unique thing about the effects are that they are stackable. For  
   instance, you can choose bubbles with explosions which will have bubbles all over the screen,and periodically explode according  
   to the beat sensitivity.

   Some cool effect combinations:
	1) Combining the "Infinite Mirror" effect and "Strobe" background results in an alternating black/white fading box effect.
	2) Combining the "Explosions" and "Infinite Mirror" effects will draw a color-changing border around the screen.
	3) In addition to filling the bubbles with their respective color, the "Fill Bubble" effect tints the background with a 	
           random color based on the beat.
	4) Selecting "None" for the background results in any current effects being drawn over each other; combining the effects    
           with "None" for the background can result in some very complex visuals.​
Right click options:
Right clicking the screen brings up an options menu where you can further interact with the program. The options for the menu are:

a. Show/Hide Song Controls
	This option toggles between showing and not showing the play, stop, clear queue, and add song buttons.

b. Show/Hide Progress Bar
	This option toggles between showing and not showing the progress bar at the bottom of the display window.
 
c. Show/Hide Options
	This option toggles between showing and not showing the options menu.

d. Play next song
	This option plays the next song in the queue.

e. Play previous song
	This option plays the song that was just before the current playing song in the queue.

f. Exit
	This option allows you to exit the program.